http://www.ghmagency.com/about/privacy-policy

800-244-9046
Search
Call Today!
800-244-9046
Menu
Personal Insurance Homeowners Discounts FAQs Flood Insurance Items in Storage Loss Assessment for Condos Auto Discounts FAQs Split Limits vs Combined Single Limits
Life & Disability Life Insurance Life Insurance FAQs Life Insurance Glossary Disability Insurance Disability FAQs Bundle to Save Business Insurance Business Auto Liability Building & Equipment Ordinance & Law, Demolition, Debris Removal Property & Tenant Improvements Replacement Cost, Functional Building Value and Actual Cash Value Employment, Commercial General & Benefit Liability Workers' Compensation Earthquake & Flood Business Income/Extra Expense Umbrella Liability Crime Coverage Cyber Liability Fiduciary Liability Inland Marine Surety Bonds Employee Benefits Health Insurance Health Insurance Glossary Life & Disability Craft Beverage HR Consulting HR Services The HR Team Specialty Programs Cannabis Insurance Land Trust Insurance Farm Insurance Nonprofit Insurance Nonprofit Insurance FAQs Client Services Claims Glass Procedures COVID-19 Information
Carriers In The News In Your Community Quotes for Community About Contact Team
Carriers In The News In Your Community Quotes for Community About Contact Team
About Contact
Privacy Policy
At GHM Agency, protecting your privacy is very important to us. We want you to understand the types of information we collect and how we use it. We collect and use nonpublic personal information in order to provide you with a broad range of insurance products and services effectively and as conveniently as possible. We treat nonpublic personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy.
As part of providing you with insurance products and services, we may obtain nonpublic personal information about you directly from you through applications, forms, and questionnaires you complete, photo's and property inspections, claim information from you and others, as well as various information you provide to us, whether in writing, in person, by telephone, fax, electronically, or from others about your transactions with us or with others. We may receive information from consumer reporting agencies, including but not limited to motor vehicle reports, claim information reports, credit scores, credit reports, financial reports, court records, tax records or other public records. We may receive information about you from others depending upon the nature of your insurance transaction, including but not limited to banks, credit unions, auto dealerships, insurance carriers, or others.
In the course of providing insurance products and services to you, which includes but is not limited to shopping your insurance policy(s) with the various insurance carriers we represent, we may disclose to others, including but not limited to insurance carriers, insurance brokers, insurance agents, mortgage bankers, credit unions, and other service providers, all of the information that we collect about you, as described above, however, we do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our clients or former clients to anyone, except as permitted by law.
This Privacy Policy applies to insurance products provided through GHM Agency used primarily for, but not limited to, personal insurance, business insurance, life insurance, disability insurance, long term care insurance, and employee benefits. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy, and any policies described above, at any time. The examples contained within the Privacy Policy are illustration; they are not intended to be exclusive. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy please contact us at GHM Agency - P.O. Box 649 - Waterville ME 04903-0649.
Contact Claim Bill Pay Forms
T: 800-244-9046F: 207-873-5784
info@ghmagency.com
51 Main StreetWaterville, Maine 04901Get DirectionsNeed to Make a Claim?Acadia Insurance 800-244-9446AllstateReport Online 800-255-7828Dairyland InsuranceAuto: 800-225-1390Cycle: 800-325-9559Foremost Insurance GroupReport Online800-527-3907The Hanover Insurance GroupReport Online800-628-0250The HartfordReport Online800-243-5860Business Insurance: 800-327-3636Jewelers Mutual Insurance CompanyReport Online800-558-6411MEMICReport Online800-636-4292MMG Insurance888-343-0533 (M-F, 8:00-4:30)888-869-8700 (after hours)Patriot Insurance CompanyReport Online866-460-1776Patrons Insurance800-542-7032Peerless Insurance800-522-7152Philadelphia Insurance Companies800-873-4552ProgressiveReport Online800-776-4737TravelersReport Online (Personal)Personal Insurance: 800-252-4633Report Online (Business)Business Insurance: 800-832-7839Union Mutual of VermontReport to GHM: 207-873-5101Want to Pay a Bill?Acadia Insurance Pay OnlineCall GHM: 800-244-9046 AllstatePay Online800-901-1732Bristol WestPay Online1-888-888-0080Dairyland InsurancePay Online800-334-0090Foremost Insurance GroupPay Online800-532-4221The Hanover Insurance GroupPay Online800-573-1187 The HartfordPay Online800-624-5578Jewelers Mutual Insurance CompanyPay Online800-558-6411 Liberty Mutual Pay Online 1-800-824-7317 MEMICPay Online800-660-1306MMG InsurancePay Online888-664-2455Patriot Insurance CompanyPay Online866-460-1776Patrons InsurancePay Online866-611-7887 Peerless InsurancePay Online800-228-7830Philadelphia Insurance CompaniesPay Online877-438-7459ProgressivePay Online800-776-4737TravelersPay Online800-842-5075 Union Mutual of VermontPay Online800-300-5261 ext. 721  Vermont MutualPay Online800-231-7820Frequently Requested FormsComing soon...
Staff Directory
Sign-up for eNews from GHM!
Go!
Thank you for signing up!
Need Help? Search GHM Site:
Search
© Copyright 2020 GHM Agency Insurance. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy
/
Website Privacy
